<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://aandrewjeski.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://aandrewjeski.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-08-08T21:32:38-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://aandrewjeski.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mountain Zen: Programming in the Montana Wilderness]]></title>
    <link href="http://aandrewjeski.github.io/blog/2014/08/06/mountain-zen-programming-in-the-montana-wilderness/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-06T16:40:42-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://aandrewjeski.github.io/blog/2014/08/06/mountain-zen-programming-in-the-montana-wilderness</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey Everyone! This is my first blog post on Github Pages. Sorry about the generic layout, will be working on that soon!</p>

<p>A few weeks ago I graduated Launch Academy, which was one of the best experiences of my life. I barely had enough time to keep up day to day necessities let alone blog, so now I plan on making up for it.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;ve applied to at least a handful of companies in Boston, but after returning to Vegas I&rsquo;ve realized that I want to expand my opportunities. I&rsquo;m applying all over the country now.</p>

<p>I forgot how much I missed the west coast and west in general, so I&rsquo;m excited to be back for now. But if any of you employers are reading this, I honestly am open to moving anymore and love new cities, people, and environments.</p>

<p>Okay, so you might have read the title. Coding in the wilderness? Montana? Is this guy joking?</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m completely serious! I&rsquo;m going up to my mountain ranch nestled into the Salish Mountain range at the base of a majestic pass (Look it up! Therrihault Pass and Lakes).</p>

<p>Why? Because after a summer of coding for 12 hours a day indoors, I&rsquo;d like to do something different. I want to take my time and find a company I will wake up every day excited for. I&rsquo;ll still be working on my projects and skills, but I&rsquo;ll be doing it with an amazing view.</p>

<p>The funny part is, the house we have there has never had internet. In fact, its so remote that when I called the ISP I realized that I didn&rsquo;t even know our address! We don&rsquo;t even have a mailbox or a paved road.</p>

<p>The land was settled in the later 1800&rsquo;s by a hardworking Amish family (as far as I know). The original owner walked to work every day, a 30 minute drive down the mountain.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s going to be a surreal experience working in technology surrounded by the great outdoors. But I&rsquo;m looking forward to this frankenstein experience of new and old worlds and hope you follow along!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
